taragana.com 2013-05-23

# Taragana | Privacy Policy

## Subscription by email

You can safely enter your email address in the subscription form. It will never be sold to anyone for any reason. Comments You can safely enter your email address in your comments. Your email address will not be displayed. It will never be sold to anyone for any reason. Your email address may be used to notify you ( automatically by the system ) whenever there is a reply to your comments or further comments in the post you have commented. 

## Web Server Log

Your IP address is automatically logged by our Webserver. All the logs are automatically discarded every couple of weeks. Non-identifying aggregate information may be retained. 

## Use of Web Site Documents 

You may download, view, copy and print documents, including graphics incorporated in the documents, that Taragana publishes on the Site ("Documents") such as white papers, press releases, datasheets and FAQs subject to the following: (a) the Documents may be used solely for personal, informational, non-commercial purposes; and (b) the Documents may not be modified or altered in any way. Except where your use constitutes "fair use" under copyright law, you may not otherwise use, download, upload, copy, print, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, post, transmit or distribute any Documents or other Content from the Site in whole or in part without the express authorization of Taragana. 

## Anti-Spam Policy

This statement applies to those Taragana websites and services that display or link to this notice (“Services”).  Taragana prohibits the use of the Services in any manner associated with the transmission, distribution or delivery of any unsolicited bulk or unsolicited commercial e-mail ("Spam"). You may not use any Services to send Spam. You also may not deliver Spam or cause Spam to be delivered to any of Taragana's Services or customers. 

In addition, e-mail sent, or caused to be sent, to or through the Services may not: 

  * use or contain invalid or forged headers; 
  * use or contain invalid or non-existent domain names; 
  * employ any technique to otherwise misrepresent, hide or obscure any information in identifying the point of origin or the transmission path; 
  * use other means of deceptive addressing; 
  * use a third party's internet domain name, or be relayed from or through a third party's equipment, without permission of the third party; 
  * contain false or misleading information in the subject line or otherwise contain false or misleading content; 
  * fail to comply with additional technical standards described below; or
  * otherwise violate the applicable Terms of Use for the Services. 

Taragana does not authorize the harvesting, mining or collection of e-mail addresses or other information from or through the Services. Taragana does not permit or authorize others to use the Services to collect, compile or obtain any information about Taragana’s customers or subscribers, including but not limited to subscriber e-mail addresses, which are Taragana's confidential and proprietary information.

Taragana does not permit or authorize any attempt to use the Services in a manner that could damage, disable, overburden or impair any aspect of any of the Services, or that could interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of any Service. 

If Taragana believes that unauthorized or improper use is being made of any Service, it may, without notice, take such action as it, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate, including blocking messages from a particular internet domain, mail server or IP address. Taragana may immediately terminate any account on any Service which it determines, in its sole discretion, is transmitting or is otherwise connected with any e-mail that violates this policy. 

Nothing in this policy is intended to grant any right to transmit or send e-mail to, or through, the Services. Failure to enforce this policy in every instance does not amount to a waiver of Taragana's rights.

Unauthorized use of the Services in connection with the transmission of unsolicited e-mail, including the transmission of e-mail in violation of this policy, may result in civil, criminal, or administrative penalties against the sender and those assisting the sender.

## Children's Privacy

Taragana is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

## Commitment

We are committed in maintaining your privacy and are actively involved in and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Taragana's Web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. 

## Your Consent

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Taragana's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Taragana collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.
